I've looked at what's being most popular
我看了最流行的
在到目前为止的教程中
I've looked at what's being most popular
in the tutorials we've done so far at
第七名增加了额外的折痕
到目前为止，最流行的形状是
in the tutorials we've done so far at
number seven adding extra creases to pop
这是它的续集
折痕第二部分正在使用计数器
number seven adding extra creases to pop
up shapes is by far the most popular so
褶皱
柜台褶皱覆盖在
up shapes is by far the most popular so
this is a sequel to that it's adding
简介，但非常简短，
所以我只回顾其中一些，然后
this is a sequel to that it's adding
creases part two this is using counter
向您展示如何使用它们来
增强您的弹出点差
creases part two this is using counter
folds
三种基本类型
折成两半然后做成一个
folds
counter folds were covered in the
剪一折一折
像这样折起来，然后重新打开
counter folds were covered in the
introduction but just very briefly and
向上推动它，所以这是
最简单的基本弹出窗口最简单
introduction but just very briefly and
so I'll just recap some of that and then
柜台折，所以有一个你可以做
如果你想要的话，在切割下也一样
so I'll just recap some of that and then
show you how you can use those to
可以改变你的角度
进来，所以你得到一个
show you how you can use those to
enhance your pop-up spreads there are
不同形状的3D片段如此开放
向上，因此您可以通过更改角度来查看
enhance your pop-up spreads there are
three basic types take the piece of card
弄皱了就可以得到
得到两个不同的形状，你也可以
three basic types take the piece of card
fold it in half and then make a single
只需将其添加到您不喜欢的提示中
一定需要削减才能工作
fold it in half and then make a single
cut so with one cut and one crease fold
从边缘说在顶部
折成两半再加上另一折
cut so with one cut and one crease fold
it like this fold it back on itself open
就像把它折起来
打开它并弹出那个向前
it like this fold it back on itself open
it up and push it forward so this is the
他们有不同的选择
都是基于降落的第二种
it up and push it forward so this is the
most simple basic pop-up the most simple
使用两个切口和一个折痕，所以我们将
切两个长度差不多的东西
most simple basic pop-up the most simple
counter fold so there's one you can do
甚至不需要削减它们，它们可以
撕裂他们甚至不需要平行
counter fold so there's one you can do
the same below the cut if you want you
他们可以保持任何角度
在这种情况下，您可以像这样折叠
the same below the cut if you want you
could change the angle that you're
将其折叠起来，然后弹出
那个向前的你你有一个类型
could change the angle that you're
coming in at and so then you get a
的步骤，这是第二次
关于平行折痕的第三种
coming in at and so then you get a
different shaped 3d piece so open that
是一个捷径，一个长捷径，所以
这实际上是融合
different shaped 3d piece so open that
up so you can see by changing the angle
折痕机制，但这是一个变化
再次将其从末端折叠
up so you can see by changing the angle
that you've creased it out you can get
切折从切尾到
切开的末端将其折回自身打开
that you've creased it out you can get
get two different shapes you can also
它弹出它向前，所以这给
你有一个角度更多的角度
get two different shapes you can also
just add it to the tip you don't
用它们创建的这些形状进行构建
折痕谷褶皱，他们创造
just add it to the tip you don't
necessarily need the cut you can work
山褶皱，其中任何一个都可以
工作了，所以如果你拿这个你
necessarily need the cut you can work
from the edge so say at the top here
实际上可以对其进行额外切割
然后您可以将其折叠，然后
from the edge so say at the top here
fold it in half add in another fold so
打开那个，你会发现你已经
主要柜台折，然后你有
fold it in half add in another fold so
it's like this fold it back on itself
您可以添加另一个小的
与他们中的任何一个一起说，我们采取
open it up and pop that forward so
这一步在这里您可以添加一个
切到主要步骤给它几个
open it up and pop that forward so
they've got the different options this
折痕，所以您还有一点额外的步骤
在那里添加，你也可以
they've got the different options this
is all based on befalls the second kind
努力进入这些优势之一
尝试用一个简短的捷径和一个
is all based on befalls the second kind
uses two cuts and one crease so we'll
更长一点，所以当你弯曲
您会看到如何玩这些游戏
uses two cuts and one crease so we'll
make two cuts about the same length you
只是其中任何一个的例子
技术可以应用于其他流行音乐
make two cuts about the same length you
don't even need to cut them they can be
改变其他机制的影响
折或谷折，你可以切这些
don't even need to cut them they can be
torn they don't even need to be parallel
进入他们，然后这些
他们可以使用的飞机，你可以坚持
torn they don't even need to be parallel
they can be at any angle it'll still
碎片放在上面使碎片站立起来
坚持做你想做什么
they can be at any angle it'll still
work in this case you fold it like this
我将展示一些示例
你们这里是小红人
work in this case you fold it like this
fold it back on itself and when you pop
骑马工程与纸工程
布鲁斯·福斯特（Bruce Foster）
fold it back on itself and when you pop
that one forward you you've got a type
有一个很小的，但这是一个v形折叠
这是过去的反折
that one forward you you've got a type
of step so that's the second time this
建在这里，然后折叠
它的其中一架飞机被用来
of step so that's the second time this
is about parallel creases the third kind
举起这多余的一块，然后在这里
好吧，这又很小，我们已经
is about parallel creases the third kind
is one short cut and one long one so
折叠成V形，并带有反折
进入它，它已经被用来提起
is one short cut and one long one so
this is actually the it's the converging
这架飞机这是cookie计数依据
Robertsóbuda，在此示例中
this is actually the it's the converging
crease mechanism but it's a variation so
我们有一个平行的折叠
在这里内置了柜台折叠
crease mechanism but it's a variation so
again you fold it from the ends of the
那么这是坚持提出
图像，因此图像基于
again you fold it from the ends of the
cuts the fold goes from end of cut to
主要机制和我想要的最后一个
告诉你是弹出的科学怪人
cuts the fold goes from end of cut to
end of cut fold it back on itself open
David Walker的造纸工程及后
这是这里持有的标签
end of cut fold it back on itself open
it up pop it forward so this is giving
整个页面机制
而不是往后走
it up pop it forward so this is giving
you an angled to more angled planes to
前进，所以这是
柜台折成它在这里提高
you an angled to more angled planes to
build with these shapes they create
如果从后面看这个图像
您可以看到这是柜台文件夹
build with these shapes they create
creases Valley folds and they create
被切成这样的地方
那块被推进
creases Valley folds and they create
mountain folds and any of those can be
看起来好像实际上有一个
第二个在这里，所以看着它像
mountain folds and any of those can be
worked on so if you take this one you
这你可以看到有一个对折
那里提高了这个形象，还有另一个
worked on so if you take this one you
can actually make an extra cut into it
一个在那里举起这个形象，所以
相当不错的科学
can actually make an extra cut into it
and you can fold that and then as you
再次在这条线上，所以有
其中三个，所以我只告诉你
and you can fold that and then as you
open that up you find you've got the
快速如何在v形折叠上做
如果我们把基础板折好，我
open that up you find you've got the
main counter fold and then you've got
拿一张卡，这是一个基本的
B折和可爱的视角折叠
main counter fold and then you've got
another small one added to it you can do
制造
我将使标签变大，以便我们可以
another small one added to it you can do
this with any of them so say we take
在这些中形成反折，因此我们创建
像这样
this with any of them so say we take
this this step one here you can add a
这些v形折叠的关键是
你把你切掉了
this this step one here you can add a
cut to the main step give it a couple of
所有折痕相遇的地方在这里
它会掉下来，我只是
cut to the main step give it a couple of
creases so you've got a small extra step
加强这些，它将坚持下去
像这样在您的页面上
creases so you've got a small extra step
added in there like that you can also
情况下，我要保持标签
向前，这样我们就可以建立反折
added in there like that you can also
work into one of these edges we could
进入他们，所以整个作品将
像我刚才那样贴在您的页面上
work into one of these edges we could
try that with a short short cut and a
加强这些折痕，使整体
事情进展顺利而甜蜜，然后
try that with a short short cut and a
longer one so when you bend that
在粘上之前，你需要工作
拿出什么买不起的东西
you see how you can play with it these
进入其中，让我们在这里输入一个步进
或有角度的加大切割
you see how you can play with it these
are just examples where any of these
不同的长度，所以我们将有
一侧倾斜的台阶将其折回
are just examples where any of these
techniques can be applied to other pop
本身，然后在这一方面，我们将
只是有一个常规步骤，所以我们做了两个
techniques can be applied to other pop
up shapes other mechanisms any mountain
削减相同的长度
所以当这一切都打开了
up shapes other mechanisms any mountain
fold or Valley fold you can cut these
将像这样工作，我们已经
也得到了这个山折
fold or Valley fold you can cut these
into them and then these any of these
中间，所以我们做了一些削减
一顶帽子可能就好了
into them and then these any of these
planes they can be used you can stick
把它折下来这么少
让我们在顶部再添加一个
planes they can be used you can stick
pieces onto them to make pieces stand up
或只是在其中折叠一点
产生更多的飞机，我们
pieces onto them to make pieces stand up
stick out do what do what you want so
可能很消耗，所以这里可以开始了
现在有了所有这些默认机制
stick out do what do what you want so
I've just got a few examples I'll show
你可以玩多近
你坚持脊椎知道什么
I've just got a few examples I'll show
you in groups here this is Little Red
塑造您想要的形状是否想要
真的很紧还是你想要它
you in groups here this is Little Red
Riding Hood with paper engineering by
更远，所以它躺下更多，
我可能会坚持下去
Riding Hood with paper engineering by
Bruce Foster and so the examples I've
向下约与脊柱成45度角
将胶水放在一边推胶水
Bruce Foster and so the examples I've
got a quite small but this is a v-fold
直到折痕不会
真的很重要
got a quite small but this is a v-fold
this is the counter fold that's been
拍打，但使它更整洁
那么这个中央折痕必须是
this is the counter fold that's been
built into it here and that counter fold
与脊椎对齐，所以有和
然后你把整张纸折叠起来
built into it here and that counter fold
one of the planes of it is being used to
胶在另一个标签上
闭合底座，使其自然
one of the planes of it is being used to
lift up this extra piece then here as
贴好位置放好
整个系列都有你的V夹
lift up this extra piece then here as
well it's again it's rather small we've
现在已添加对等点的数量
开始使用这些就可以使用
well it's again it's rather small we've
got a a V fold with a counter fold built
他们以您喜欢的任何方式，所以请这样说
你可以挺身而出
got a a V fold with a counter fold built
into it and that's been used to lift up
我们可以，也可以两者都做，所以只要
其中之一以这种方式，其中之一
into it and that's been used to lift up
this plane this is cookie count by
每当您添加一个
一块建筑总是关闭它
this plane this is cookie count by
Roberts óbuda and in this example here
向下并确保它会
工作，但它将适合
Roberts óbuda and in this example here
we've got this is a parallel fold here's
碎片不会卡在一起或
斜着这些脊柱
we've got this is a parallel fold here's
the counter fold built into it here and
那些在这里我们可以拿一块像
这种折叠可能会在中间折叠
the counter fold built into it here and
then this is sticking out raising an
或者可以将其折成一端
你可以坚持一点不对称
then this is sticking out raising an
image so the image is built on to the
一块放在那里就像我们一样
走
image so the image is built on to the
main mechanism and the last one I want
而我要切的是
尖角，所以它会适合
main mechanism and the last one I want
to show you is the pop-up Frankenstein
更好地形成我们的形状
应该很好
to show you is the pop-up Frankenstein
paper engineering by David Walker and on
在那里，我们希望将其折叠
告诉您如何使用计数器
paper engineering by David Walker and on
this one here the tab that is holding
与您的其他弹出形状一起折叠
使用它们来添加额外的飞机
this one here the tab that is holding
the whole mechanism to the page rather
然后可以继续做下去
弹出窗口，我想要另一种
the whole mechanism to the page rather
than going backwards out of sight it's
向您展示实际上是
所有这些不对称的
than going backwards out of sight it's
coming forward and so this is the
之前看过是对称的
非对称类型，您不能折痕
coming forward and so this is the
counter fold cut into it here raising
你正在事先构建的一块
必须考虑一点，所以如果我们采取
counter fold cut into it here raising
this image if you look at it from behind
这样的一块，你需要画一个
脊椎褶皱走向的指南
this image if you look at it from behind
you can see this is the counter folders
是这样，让我们​​只说这是哪里
脊椎褶皱将是然后
you can see this is the counter folders
being cut into this there's a cut there
说这是你的底部
弹出窗口将是这样
being cut into this there's a cut there
and that piece is being pushed forward
成为折痕，这将是一个
折痕，然后我们可以升高
and that piece is being pushed forward
it looks as though there's actually a
根据我们的喜好，我们将再添加一个折痕
就在这里，这将是一个折痕
it looks as though there's actually a
second one here so looking at it like
现在这是主要的脊柱褶皱
以及我们离它的距离
second one here so looking at it like
this you can see there's a counter fold
是尺子的宽度，所以我要
在这里使用相同的东西是
this you can see there's a counter fold
there raising this image there's another
重要的是，这个距离
我们称之为a与此相同
there raising this image there's another
one there raising this image so that's
距离，我们将其称为a，因此这两个
是在这里和在这里的切割线
one there raising this image so that's
quite a nicely science done
刻痕永远不能
交叉割线，割线必须
quite a nicely science done
again on on this line as well so there's
永远不要越过划线，所以这是
脊椎褶皱，所以分数从
again on on this line as well so there's
three of those so I'll just show you
切线到边缘，这是
整个施工的底部
three of those so I'll just show you
quickly how to do it on a on a v-fold so
再次从切割线到切割线
这将是领先优势
quickly how to do it on a on a v-fold so
if we take a base sheet nicely creased I
再次伸出来，你就从削减
线到线
if we take a base sheet nicely creased I
take a piece of card so this is a basic
和头一个，所以现在这将
折叠在那里，整个事情要
take a piece of card so this is a basic
B fold and a cute angle view fold I'm
挺身而出，这将是一个
山折谷折
B fold and a cute angle view fold I'm
making
底部是山谷褶皱，所以这是你的
您想看到的平行四边形
making
I'll make the tabs quite big so we can
更干净一点，我们实际上可以推动它
穿过另一边出来
I'll make the tabs quite big so we can
make counter folds in those so we create
那你就可以那样使用它
可以那样反复使用它
make counter folds in those so we create
it up like this
可以向这些添加更多的反瀑布
我们把那只猫折成一只猫
it up like this
the crucial thing with these v-folds is
向下，所以有平行四边形和
还有鸟儿，这是增加寻找的步骤
the crucial thing with these v-folds is
that you you cut away up to the point
有关这些的更多信息，您可以看看我的
书籍弹出式设计和纸张力学
that you you cut away up to the point
where all the creases meet so here it is
而这恰恰相反
更深入
where all the creases meet so here it is
it's going to stick down I'll just
您